Hello friends welcome to Share Market Location, this is your
first time on the channel so please
like, subscribe and share the channel.
Friends, I have uploaded a video about the
latest partnership with Ashok Leyland
and the latest news on Shri Remedies from Shri Karne,
go and watch it too. Friends, let's
start the
video. Friends, ICICI Lombard
Insurance, you all know that the insurance
sector has been with us for a long time, it is not doing well for the last two-three years,
like ICICI
Lombard Insurance, HDFC Life
Insurance, it is
not doing well for two years, but now the
target is being given in it. Look here
HDFC Securities has given 1270 to ICICI Lombard
and this is very good news,
although the company is a very good company,
friends, and its target is being
given at 1207. Friends
[Music]
now let's see how it is doing. How is the
share price of ICICI Lombard, it is
running around 1200, the target
is 1265. Friends, the company has not given any significant return in one year, the
entire insurance sector
is in decline.
So like and subscribe the video,
see you soon in the next video,
thank you.